Hey guys, so we are in the end of privilege legislation section and let's talk about one more
method called always install elevator so this configuration if you if you sit the always
install elevator to enable to mode basically when you want to install any Microsoft Windows
Install or MSF files it will be automatically get installed as an administrator level privilege
but it here some limited permissions okay basically so let me go one more time if you enable
the always install elevator so whatever applications like MSF not MSF files Microsoft Windows
installer files if you are installing in Windows it will be automatically get installed as an
administrator level privilege okay so let me show you how to enable that let me go to a run
and you have to go for a gp edd.msc so inside that we have a set of configuration let me explore
maximize this let me go to the administrator template Windows components go to the
windows installer so here you can find there is an option called always install elevator
okay privilege when you enable this double click on that you can enable enable from here
when you enable this privilege or whatever Windows whatever Windows applications like
not MSF files you are installing it will be automatically get installed as a administrator privilege
okay let me set it to apply and I will be giving okay
so now it has been enabled let me go to the registry key ones and I will check
few more things
yeah oh it was not here so now whatever application dot MSF files you are installing it will be
automatically get installed as an administrator level privilege okay this is one kind of
a privilege escalation it will be mostly focusing on our user tools like medium and
entry level to the high mandatory level because we are going to user to administer
the level privilege so you can you can enable the settings to do that okay so that's all
about this video a certain speed video we'll hop off and we'll continue our discussion next video
You guys, bye-bye.